Front-end web UI frameworks are increasingly becoming the approach for
前端 web 界面框架正逐渐成为
designing and implementing websites quickly.
快速设计和实现网页的方法
Let's examine some details of front-end web UI frameworks in this lecture.
在这个课程中 我们将会学习到 前端 web 界面框架的许多细节
We last covered service.
前面我们讲到了服务
What are front-end web UI frameworks?
那么什么是前端 web 界面框架 ?
Then we'll look at why we would be interested in using a front-end framework
然后我们会学习 为什么我们需要用一个前端框架
and finally a list of the popular front-end web UI frameworks.
最后 我们则会学习到 有哪些流行的前端界面框架
What exactly do front-end web UI frameworks provide for you?
前端 web 界面框架到底提供了什么?
Now typically a front-end web UI framework is a collection Of HTML, CSS, and
通常来说 一个前端 web 界面框架 是一个 HTML, CSS 和 JavaScript 模板的集合
Javascript templates that enable you to quickly design and implement your website.
这个集合能帮助你快速地设计和实现你的网站
So they will provide a collection of components like Buttons,
比如它们会提供一系列不同的按钮
Tables, Navigation bars, Modals, Accordions,
表格 导航栏 模态版 折叠
Carousels and Dropdowns and many other features.
轮播和下拉菜单等许多其它东西
And also addressing Typography and color schemes for your website.
还包括提供一些排版方案和一些配色方案
Why should we be interested using front-end web UI frameworks?
那么为什么我们需要用前端 web 界面框架呢？
One of the primary reasons is responsive web design.
其中的一个主要原因是 我们可以借助它来进行响应式网页设计
Now, we will examine responsive web design in more detail in the next lecture.
在下一节课我们将会学习 响应式网页设计的细节
Here, let me quickly summarize what we mean by this.
而在这里 我会快速地概述一下 响应式网页设计的概念
We realize that people are accessing websites using various different
不能忽视的是 用户通常会在不同的设备上 浏览我们的网页
devices of different screen sizes.
而这些不同的设备通常拥有着 不同的屏幕尺寸
Now how do we target these different screen sizes by using a single website
如何针对不同屏幕的大小 而采用统一的设计
design and make our website automatically adapt to different screen sizes.
使其能自动调整网页内容的显示
So that is one of the primary issues being addressed by responsive web design.
这是响应式网页设计的核心问题之一
In particular, we see an increasing trend towards mobile first.
而事实上 潮流是 移动优先
Meaning that first, design your website with the mobile screen size in mind,
移动优先的意思是 优先考虑移动屏幕的网页设计
and then adapt to larger screen sizes from there.
然后再将其改编以适应更大的屏幕
We'll also look at mobile first design in more detail in the next lecture.
我们同样会在下一节课上学习 移动优先设计的细节
A second reason why you might be interested in front-end frameworks,
第二个你应该用前端框架的原因是
is that different browsers have different quirks in them.
不同的浏览器可能会有不同特异的地方
So we need a way of commonly targeting all the different browsers so
所以我们需要一个方法
that our website renders uniformly independent
让所有的浏览器
of which browser a user uses to access our website.
都能成功地渲染我们的网页
Now addressing the quirks of different browsers is not that straightforward.
但是 逐一地处理这些浏览器的奇同之处 并非直接了当
Fortunately for us,
幸运的是
these frameworks have already taken care of addressing these issues so
这些前端框架已经提供了这些异同之处的解决方案
that it becomes straightforward for us to concentrate on our website design.
所以我们可以专心于网站的设计
And if we make use of the front-end frameworks, they will automatically take
因为在你使用前端框架时
care of the problems of addressing the different browser issues.
它们会帮你解决不同浏览器间的兼容问题
A third and equally important reason for
第三个同样重要的原因是
using a front-end framework is increased productivity.
应用前端框架可以提高你的效率
Now designing websites, from the scratch, is quite cumbersome.
事实上 从零开始搭建网站是一项 非常枯燥且繁杂的任务
Now, because these front-end frameworks provide us with a lot of
而如果你应用前端框架的话
features and competence, it becomes more straightforward to design our website
你会发现它已经实现了很多功能 这些功能 具有视觉和感觉上的一致性
with a consistent look and feel.
而你需要做的只是去调用它们
Finally, let's not underestimate the community support that
注意 我们不能忽视一个前端框架背后的
a front-end framework enjoys.
社区支持
Now, the larger the community that participates in a front-end framework,
显然 一个前端框架背后的社区越大
the larger the resources that we have available to us that we can leverage to
这个前端框架就会支持越多的功能
address issues that we might encounter in using a front-end framework.
来让我们解决我们遇到的问题
You might find a lot of examples out there, you might find people posting
在社区中你会发现有许多样例 和大家发布的帖子
blog entries addressing various features.
阐述不同的功能
That is very very important when you need to quickly get started
这些支持在你需很快开始实施你的网站时
implementing a website.
无疑是非常重要的
Finally let's look at some of the popular front-end frameworks.
最后 让我们来看一下有哪些流行的前端框架
Now this is a small list.
如图所示是一个小的列举
There are a large number of front-end frameworks out there.
而事实上前端框架的数量 要比这里列举的要多得多
I'm giving you the list of the most popular among them.
我所列举的只是其中最有名的一些框架
Now, again, I might have missed out your favorite front-end web framework.
呃 当然我可能会漏掉了你最喜欢的 前端 web 框架
Don't get too worked up about it.
希望你不要太激动
People have different opinions on this.
毕竟这些东西都是众说纷纭
Now this is one of the most opinionated areas of website design.
而这是网站设计中最各持己见的话题
People tend to hang on to their favorite web UI frameworks and
人们都会坚持用他们最喜欢的 web 界面框架
insist that that is the best way to address the problem.
并坚持声称那个框架是最好的
Again, we should all take this with a big grain of salt.
所以我们需要做的是保持客观并有保留地 吸收他们的意见
Maybe I should say a big rock of salt after all, but anyway.
可能我得再次强调一下"有保留"这三个字
Based upon looking at several different plug entries,
总之 当我看了许多框架的接口后
this is the list that I feel comfortable with in presenting to you.
我选出了如图所示的这些我认为 你比较适合拿来使用的框架
One of the most popular of all the front-end frameworks is of
而这其中最流行的框架之一
course Bootstrap.
就是 Bootstrap 了
We'll look at Bootstrap in more detail In the subsequent lectures.
而它也正是我们会在接下来的一系列课程中 详细学习的对象
Foundation by Zurb is yet another popular framework, has a pretty large following.
Foundation by Zurb 也是另一个很有名的框架 也有很多人在用
Then we have Semantic UI which is gaining a lot of ground.
然后就是 Semantic UI 被日益采用
Pure by Yahoo, UI Kit, and many more.
Pure, UI Kit 等等等等
Now, when you look at these frameworks, you will notice that they have a lot
而事实上 当你了解了这些框架后
in common, and each one of these frameworks have some unique features.
你会发现其实它们有很多相同的地方 不过当然 也有一些独特之处
Now, your choice of a framework is dictated more by what you're trying
你需要注意的是 不要执着于
to achieve than trying to stick to one single framework for all your needs.
用单一的框架去实现所有的功能
Again, look at it as possibilities that you have for you.
记住这些框架都是可能的选择
Getting started with any one of these frameworks is not that difficult
其实 只要你有应用其中一个框架的经验的话
once you have a quick introduction to one of those frameworks.
从头开始应用任何一个框架都不会太难
Many of them have common features as a set.
它们在很多方面都是类似的
So it should not be very difficult to switch from one framework to another if
所以当你发现另一个框架会更好地适应 你当前的需求的话
you'll find that a second one is better suited for your purpose.
那么转换到另一框架 难度不会太大
So now we will go onto the next set of lectures where we'll examine
接下来我们将开始后续的课程
Bootstrap in more detail.
将会学习 Bootstrap 的细节 翻译: Carefree0910 | 审阅: Saul Qunming Yuan Coursera Global Translator Community